[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the only President who had a patent?", "correct_answer": "Lincoln", "incorrect_answers": ["Hoover", "Jefferson", "Washington"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is a technique or method of dyeing fabrics using wax (to cover parts of the fabric not intended to be dyed).", "correct_answer": "batik", "incorrect_answers": ["susak", "barak", "kurak"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The platypus needs to eat around 10% of its own weight every day.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the 1962 film about the planet Uranus?", "correct_answer": "Journey to the Seventh Planet", "incorrect_answers": ["Meet me on Uranus", "Escaping the Blue Planet", "I Love Uranus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This special kind of clover, originally used in medicine, is the national flower of Ireland.", "correct_answer": "Shamrock", "incorrect_answers": ["Cosmos", "Caladium", "Celosia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the best selling album of all time in the United States as of 2007?", "correct_answer": "The Eagles Greatest Hits 1971-1975", "incorrect_answers": ["The Wall, by Pink Floyd", "Thriller, by Michael Jackson", "Led Zeppelin IV, by Led Zeppelin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first e-mail message was sent in this year by Ray Tomlinson.", "correct_answer": "1971", "incorrect_answers": ["1979", "1964", "1983"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is said to have carried chocolate with him on military campaigns?", "correct_answer": "Napoleon", "incorrect_answers": ["Caesar", "George Patton", "Alexander the Great"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these terms denotes an insertion of an object underneath the skin to create a raised design?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["3-D implantation", "Subdermal implantation", "Pocketing"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the US, why do we change our clocks on the daylight saving time dates in April and October?", "correct_answer": "To conserve energy", "incorrect_answers": ["To increase the hours of the day", "To extend the working day", "Because the tourist period in most countries starts in May"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Match this definition to the word it belongs in Ambrose Bierce\u2019s book The Devils Dictionary: \u201ca machine which you go into as a pig and come out of as a sausage.\u201d", "correct_answer": "Litigation", "incorrect_answers": ["A Sausage Factory", "Life", "Marriage"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the building block of green plants that cant be broken down into sugar molecules and passes through the human body undigested?", "correct_answer": "dietary fiber", "incorrect_answers": ["glucose", "dextrose", "fructose"]}]